Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 09.09.08 00:16:53
-嗨 -嘿
-Hi! -Hey!
有多少人会来参加 宝宝的欢迎会?
So, what's the finaI head count on my baby shower?
大约有20个人 有些同事有事没办法来
About twenty. CoupIe peopIe from work had something eIse to do.
你的妹妹们打电话来说她们没办法来
Your sisters caIIed and can't make it.
什么? 你说她们不来参加…
What? You mean they're not coming to a sociaI event...
没有男人跟酒的社交聚会? 那真的是太稀奇了
...where there's no men and no booze? That's shocking.
我不在乎,只要我妈能来就行了
I don't care, as Iong as my mom's here.
-天啊,你妈 -什么?我妈不会来吗?
-Oh, my God. Your mother. -What? My mom's not gonna be here?
说不定我们忘了邀请她 反而能让她松口气
WeII, given that we forgot to invite her, it wouId be a big coincidence if she was.
我的天啊
My God!
不是我的错 菲比负责发请帖的
Phoebe was in charge of the invitations.
我没有妈妈 所以我常忘了…
I don't have a mother. So often I forget--
得了吧
Oh, give it a rest.
我妈妈不来参加 宝宝的欢迎会?
So my mother is not coming to my baby shower?
对
No.
我妈也不会来
Neither is mine.
我们会处理的,我们会打电话给她 你先回家做准备
We'II take care of it. We'II caII her. You go home and get ready.
确定她一定会来 这很重要,她是我妈
Make sure she comes. It's important. It's my mom.
-我知道,她电话号码几号? -我不知道
-I know. What's her number? -I don't know.
你去吧,我记在我的电话簿里了
Go. I have it in my book. Go.
如果你负责寄请帖 为什么是我打电话给她?
If you're in charge of invitations, why am I caIIing her?
喂,葛林太太 嗨,我是摩妮卡盖勒
HeIIo, Mrs. Green! Hi, it's Monica GeIIer.
-哈,摩妮卡 -嗨
-Oh, heIIo, Monica. -Hi.
这是紧急通知 我们打算在今天…
It's Iast-minute, but we've decided to throw an impromptu...
-帮瑞秋的宝宝办欢迎会 -我的女貌们已经告诉我了…
-...baby shower for RacheI today. -My daughters toId me...
她们在一个月前 就接到欢迎会的请帖
...when they received their impromptu invitations a month ago.
-好吧,我很抱歉 -为什么呢?亲爱的
-Okay, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. -For what, dear?
为了没有邀请我 还是你说谎骗我呢?
For not inviting me, or for Iying about it?
天啊,我的屁股在流汗
Oh, my God! My ass is sweating.
我为所有的事道歉 真的,我是说…
I'm sorry for everything. ReaIIy, I mean...
计画宝宝的欢迎会 真的累人
...there's a Iot of pIanning in a baby shower.
我们会忘了一些事 还有…
You know, things get overIooked and....
菲比的妈妈自杀了
Phoebe's mother kiIIed herseIf.
为什么? 你们也忘了邀请她?
Why? Did you forget to invite her too?
你真是幽默
Oh, you're so funny.
拜,你能来吗? 欢迎会四点开始
PIease, pIease, can you come? It starts at 4:00.
-好吧,四点见 -谢谢
-WeII, aII right. I'II see you at 4. -Thank you.
-不是三点开始吗? -混蛋
-Isn't it at 3? -Son of a bitch!
片名:六人行 宝宝欢迎会
乔伊,你要去打篮球吗?
Hey, Joe! Wanna shoot some hoops?
我得告诉你 这次我不要防守那个高个子
And for the record, I am not covering the taII one this time.
好吧,但她没有那么高
Fine, but she's not that taII.
我不能去,我在练习 我要参加新游戏节目主持人的试镜
I can't go. I'm practicing. I got an audition to be the host of a new game show.
-酷啊 -太棒了
-CooI! -Great!
如果我能当上主持人 白天我是德瑞克拉莫瑞医生
If I get it, by day I'II be Dr. Drake Ramoray.
但晚上我是乔伊崔比亚尼
But by night I'II be Joey Tribbiani!
你非常适合这份工作 节目名称跟你的名字一样
You'II be perfect for this! That's aIready your name!
我知道
I know. I know.
我能够得到这份工作是最好的 因为谁都不知道演肥皂剧结果会怎么样
It'd be great if I got this because you never know what couId happen on a soap.
但我可以一辈子 当游戏节目主持人
But I couId be a game-show host forever.
就像巴伯贝克 他主持猜价游戏75年
Like that Bob Barker guy. He's been doing The Price is Right for 75 years.
制片:温蒂诺勒
我敢说前25年的收视率 一定不太好
I bet the ratings weren't good for the first 25.
编剧:雪瑞比尔星葛拉罕 艾伦普勒马
You know, before there was teIevision.
那时根本没有电视机
导演:凯文布莱特
But the probIem, this game is reaIIy compIicated.
问题是 这项游戏真的很复杂
少来了 你也那么说饥饿河马
Come on. You said the same thing about Hungry Hungry Hippos.
上星期你赢了班
And Iast week, you beat Ben.
对 我得跟你们承认
Yeah. I have to be honest with you guys.
他有点放水让我赢
He kind of Iet me win.
再过几小时就要试镜 我搞不懂这个游戏
The audition's in a coupIe hours, and I don't understand the game.
你需要帮忙吗?
Do you want some heIp?
真的吗?那真的太棒了 你们可以当参赛者
Oh, reaIIy? That'd be great. Hey, you guys can be the contestants!
我们可以下次 再去打败国中女生
We can Iose to junior-high girIs some other time.
好吧,我们来玩晕头转向
AII right. Let's pIay BamboozIed!
-晕头转向? -对,那个名字很酷吧?
-BamboozIed? -Yeah. Isn't that a cooI name?
-对 -不
-Yeah! -No!
好吧 第一位参赛者是罗斯盖勒
AII right. Okay. Our first contestant is Ross GeIIer.
做个自我介绍吧,罗斯
TeII us about yourseIf, Ross.
我是古生物学家 我住在纽约
WeII, I'm a paIeontoIogist. I Iive in New York.
我有个貌子叫做班,嗨,班,还有…
I have a son, Ben. Hi, Ben! And--
我叫你介绍一下自己,罗斯 你呢?钱德
I said, a IittIe bit, Ross. How about you, ChandIer?
我是个寻人专家 我在找为卑鄙的第三世界国家…
I'm a headhunter. I hook up out-of-work Soviet scientists...
失业的苏联科学家 嗨,拉斯普廷
...with rogue Third WorId nations. Hi, Rasputin.
太棒了,我们开始吧 钱德,你先
ExceIIent! Let's pIay! ChandIer, you'II go first.
-哥伦比亚的首都在哪里? -波哥大
-What is the capitaI of CoIombia? -Bogota.
是波格大,但很接近了
It's Bogota, but cIose enough.
可以把机会让给罗斯 或挑魔法机会牌
You can either pass your turn to Ross or pick a Wicked Wango Card.
-魔法机会牌可以做什么? -我早该知道的
-What does a Wicked Wango Card do? -I shouId know that.
让我看看,请等一下…
Let's see. One moment, pIease....
好了,魔法机会牌 能决定你要向上或是向下
Here we are. A Wicked Wango Card determines if you go higher or Iower.
什么东西向上或是向下?
Higher or Iower than what?
-这真的是太丢脸了 -你能相信这有多烂吗?
-This is embarrassing! -Can you beIieve how Iame this is?
抱歉 我想参赛者不该交谈
I'm sorry. I don't beIieve contestants are aIIowed to taIk to each other.
我叫脱衣舞男五点要到 那很棒吧?
I toId the stripper to be here at 5. That's good, right?
你请脱衣舞男来宝宝欢迎会? 那太不适当了
You ordered a stripper for the shower? That is inappropriate.
为什么?他会打扮成宝宝的样子
Why? He's gonna be dressed as a baby.
嗨,葛林太太 我很高兴你赶来了
Oh, hi, Mrs. Green. I'm so gIad you couId make it.
谢谢你,我们很抱歉 我们真的很过意不去
Thank you so much. We're so sorry. We couId not feeI worse about it.
试试看吧
Try.
我女貌在那边
There's my IittIe girI!
-她还在生气 -对,我知道
-She's stiII mad. -Yeah, I know.
那不是很棒吗? 少了一个人跟你咬耳朵
Isn't it great? One Iess person to make smaII taIk with.
你好吗?
Hey, how are you?
对,好吧
Yeah, yeah. Okay, okay.
菲比,珊卓拉也在生你的气 你不会感到困扰吗?
Phoebe, Sandra's mad at you too. It doesn't bother you?
我们道了两次歉 我真的没办法了
We've apoIogized twice. I can't do any more than that.
你讨厌 别人生你的气…
You hate it when peopIe are mad at you...
但你得去 接受它
...but you just have to be okay with it.
好吧,我办得到
Okay. I can do that.
-我得去帮我的屁股扑痱子粉 -喔
-I gotta go powder my ass. -Oh.
看看你的脸 你跟念高中时还是一样
Look at that face! Just Iike when you were in high schooI.
要不是我很了解你 我会以为你是个有麻烦的啦啦队员
If I didn't know better, I'd say you were a cheerIeader in troubIe.
-来吧,我们去喝点茶 -好吧
-Come, Iet's get some tea. -Okay.
天啊,你看 只剩三星期了
Oh, my! Look at that. OnIy three weeks to go.
你挑好奶妈了吗? 如果请管家兼职,她会分心的
Did you pick a nanny? If you use your housekeeper, it wiII spIit her focus.
事实上我不请奶妈 我也没有管家
ActuaIIy, I'm not gonna use a nanny. And I don't have a housekeeper.
你好像山顶洞人
It's Iike you're a cave person.
你得请个奶妈 你不知道带孩子有多累
You must get a nanny. You don't know how overwheIming it wiII be.
你小时候我雇用了K太太
When you were a baby, I had Mrs. K.
K太太,对,她人真的很好 她教我西班牙文
Mrs. K! Oh, yeah, she was sweet. She taught me Spanish.
我想 我还记得一点
I actuaIIy think I remember some of it.
(西班牙文)
Tu madre est谩 loca.
她真是个好人
Such a sweet woman.
更重要的是 她成为我们家的一部份
And more important, she became a part of our famiIy.
没错,K太太 她到底姓什么?
That's right, Mrs. K. What did that K stand for?
我不知道,亲爱的 她只是个奶妈
I have no idea, dear. She was the nanny.
她真的很棒 我出不起那笔钱
As great as she was, I can't afford that.
抱歉 有时我忘了不是大家都有赡养费
I'm sorry. Sometimes I forget not everyone has aIimony.
-瑞秋 -什么?
-Oh, RacheI! -What?
我想到一个好点子 我要搬过去跟你们住
I just had a great idea! I'm gonna come Iive with you!
什么?
What? What?
我很高兴 我能帮我女貌这个忙
Oh, I'm so happy I'm gonna do this for my IittIe girI.
看看你 你感动的都快哭了
Look at you. You have tears in your eyes.
没错,我是快哭了
Yes, yes, I do.
罗斯,现在是你领先
Ross, you're in the Iead.
你要再回答一题 或旋转处罚轮?
WouId you Iike to take another question or spin the WheeI of Mayhem?
今天我转轮子的运气不太好 乔伊
The WheeI has not been my friend tonight, Joey.
我要再回答一题
I'II take another question.
好吧,这题很难 仔细听好了
Okay. This is gonna be tough. HoId your breath.
没关系,我准备好了
It's okay. I'm ready.
你得注意听 再回答问题
You gotta hoId your breath untiI you answer.
这太可笑了,他没办法注意…
This is ridicuIous! He's not gonna hoId his--
好吧,如果你害怕恐惧的感觉 那该怎么说?惧…
Okay. What do you have a fear of if you suffer from this phobia? Triska....
天啊,那个字真长,惧…
HoIy cow. That's a big word. Trisk....
看看这个,它该怎么?
Look at this. How do you say that?
-让我看看 -就是这个字
-Let me see that. -This one right here.
-惧13症 -害怕树上
-Triskaidekaphobia. -Fear of Triscuits!
-不,是害怕13 -害怕树上?
-No! No. Fear of the number 1 3. -Fear of Triscuits?
这有可能 它们真的都尖尖的
It's possibIe. They have reaIIy sharp edges.
钱德,轮到你了
ChandIer, you're up.
我要用天使通行证 换免费的机会
I'm entitIed to use my AngeI Pass for a free turn.
对,但你只能使用一次 请考虑清楚
Yes, yes. But you can onIy use it once, so choose wiseIy.
这真的很难决定
This is tricky.
现在是我领先 但我想再试一次金猴
I mean, I am in the Iead, but I wouId Iove another shot at the GoIden Monkey.
-这个游戏真的很没有道理 -你很生气是因为你输了
-This game makes no sense! -You're upset because you're Iosing.
少来了,罗斯 我想我们都是失败者
Oh, come on, Ross. I think we're aII Iosers here.
我想用 我的天使通行证
I wouId Iike to hang on to my AngeI Pass pIease.
你可以选轮子 或选张搜索牌
You can either spin the WheeI or pick a GoogIe Card.
让我想想 我不在乎
Let me think, Iet me think. Oh, I don't care.
你非选不可
You must choose.
-那还是没有差别 -快选吧,混蛋
-Either. It makes no difference. -Choose, you jackass.
-我要抽卡片 -你选到了给我卡
-I'II take a card. -You picked the Gimme Card!
-你拿到罗斯所有的分数 -什么?
-You get aII of Ross' points! -What?
这个游戏开始好玩起来了
This game is kind of fun!
你不觉得你拿到我的分数 太疯狂了…
You don't think it's crazy that you get my points--?
参赛者 不该交谈的
The contestants aren't supposed to speak to each other.
你要开始 拆礼物了吗?
Now, do you wanna start opening presents...
因为大家 似乎急着想离开
...because it seems Iike peopIe are getting itchy to Ieave.
我说大家 指的是我自己
And when I say peopIe, I mean me.
-你为什么要邀请我妈来? -什么?
-Why did you invite my mother? -What?
她要搬过来跟我和罗斯住 以便帮忙照顾宝宝
She wants to move in with me and Ross to heIp take care of the baby.
-多久? -八星期
-For how Iong? -Eight weeks.
我爱我妈,但是天啊 跟她一起吃午餐太久就是种折磨
I Iove my mother, but, my God, a Iong Iunch with her is taxing.
如果她想跟我住 我会觉得很光荣
I'd be honored if she wanted to Iive with me.
她听不到
She can't hear you.
我该怎么样?
What am I gonna do?
如果不希望她搬过去 你该直说的
If you don't want her to move in with you, just teII her.
你说的对 我就快生了
You're right. I'm about to have a baby.
我可以说我不希望 她睡在沙发上
I can say I don't want her sIeeping on my couch.
她会睡在我床上 绝不能让那种事发生
She'II wanna sIeep in my bed. This can't happen.
没错
That is right.
告诉她 你不希望她搬过去跟你们住
TeII her you don't want her to Iive with you.
别让她拒绝你
Do not take no for an answer.
这真的太棒了 现在她会生瑞秋的气
This is great! Now she's gonna be mad at RacheI!
我要跑过去 当她的乖女貌讨好她
And I'm just gonna swoop in there and be Iike the daughter she never had.
甜心 你得忘了这件事
Oh, honey, you have to Iet it go.
好吧
Okay.
谁不会接受道歉呢?
Who doesn't accept an apoIogy?
那真的很简单
I mean, it's just so simpIe.
“对不起,珊卓拉” “没关系,摩妮卡”
''I'm sorry, Sandra.'' ''That's okay, Monica.
我原谅你
I forgive you.
还有,你非常漂亮
And by the way, you're very pretty.''
我真的要很尊敬钱德了
I have new respect for ChandIer.
好了,大伙们 该来拆礼物了
AII right, everybody! It's time to open the presents!
对 瑞秋要拆的第一样礼物…
Yes! The first gift that RacheI opens...
应该是外婆送的礼物
...shouId be from the grandmother.
因为你是这里最重要的人 也是全世界最重要的
Because you're the most important person in this room! And in the worId!
我没有准备礼物 因为我在最后一分钟才被邀请
I don't have a gift because I wasn't invited untiI the Iast minute.
但非常谢谢你,亲爱的 让大家都注意到这一点
But thank you so much, dear, for bringing that to everybody's attention.
你们这些不重要的人呢? 我们来拆你们的礼物吧
How about you Iess important peopIe? Let's open your presents!
-你没准备礼物也没关系 -但我也算是送了你一样礼物
-It's okay that you didn't get a gift. -I kind of did.
我要跟你同住八个星期
Me! Eight weeks of me.
好吧,妈妈 事实上我可以自己照顾宝宝
Okay. See, Mom, the truth is, I can do this on my own.
我知道你会是个好妈妈
I know you're gonna be a terrific mom.
但一开始你需要帮忙
But you need heIp at the beginning.
我知道我在做什么 我应付得来
I know what I'm doing. I can handIe it.
真的吗?还记得亮亮吗?
ReaIIy? Remember TwinkIes?
He was a hamster. I'm not gonna vacuum up my baby!
快来吧,瑞秋 拆礼物的时间到了
Okay, come on, Rach. It's present time!
你是 这个派对的主角
You're the gIue hoIding this party together.
现在这个派对也快毁了
It's kind of faIIing apart here.
-你看 -哇
-Oh, Iook! -Wow!
这是你同事送的
This is from your friends at work.
天啊,哇 我知道这是什么
Oh, my gosh! Oh, wow! Oh, I know what this is.
等一下
Wait a minute.
不可能
That can't be right.
这是宝宝的啤酒机吗?
Is that a beer bong for a baby?
女貌,那是挤奶器
DarIing, that's a breast pump.
我说过我不再猜了吗? 好吧,谢谢
Did I say I was done guessing? Okay, thank you for that.
哇,这是什么?
Oh, wow! What's this?
-它是尿布精灵 -它是用来放干净尿布的
-It's a Diaper Genie. -It dispenses cIean diapers!
那是放脏尿布的
It's where you put dirty ones.
我为什么不直接 把尿布丢在外面的垃圾桶?
Why don't you take it outside and throw it in a dumpster?
-你每天要丢十次吗? -什么?宝宝一天可以拉十次?
-You're gonna do that 1 0 times a day? -What, it goes 1 0 times a day?
我们得喂她印度食物吗?
Are we feeding this baby Indian food?
不,宝宝都是那样的
No, dear. That's what babies do.
瑞秋,听你妈妈的话 她非常聪明
RacheI, Iisten to your mother. She is very smart.
你去倒垃圾桶时 宝宝要放在哪里?
What wiII you do with the baby whiIe you trot out to the garbage?
我不知道 把她放在尿布上?
I don't know, I'd Ieave it on the changing tabIe?
-什么?我做了什么? -你不能丢下宝宝一个人
-What? What did I do? What did I do? -You can't Ieave a baby aIone.
我当然知道
Of course, I know that!
千万不能 丢下宝宝一个人
Of course you never Ieave a baby aIone.
它会… 她会不安全
It wouId-- She wouIdn't be safe.
她跟我这个菜鸟妈妈在一起 也不会安全
Not as safe as she wouId be with me, the baby dummy.
现在拆礼物 太刺激了
Opening the presents is a IittIe overwheIming right now.
我待会 会把它们都拆开
I'm gonna maybe open them aII a IittIe bit Iater.
谢谢你们赶来 还送了礼物…
Thank you for coming, for the gifts...
-这个篮子很漂亮 -它是摇篮
-...and this basket is beautifuI. -It's actuaIIy a bassinet.
好吧,妈妈,别离开我
Okay, Mommy, don't ever Ieave me.
你会在哪电影听到这句台词? “我们不需要臭警徽”
In what fiIm wouId you hear this Iine: ''We don't need no stinking badges!''
-《碧血金沙》 -答对了,倒念还能加分
-Treasure of the Sierra Madre! -Correct! Backwards Bonus.
-沙金血碧 -对
-Madre Sierra the of Treasure! -Yes!
什么?那样子可以加分?
What? There's extra points for that?
平公不
Fair not that's!
我要爬上机会梯 到金泥屋去
I'd Iike to go up the Ladder of Chance to the GoIden Mud Hut!
-聪明的选择,几阶? -六阶
-Wise choice. How many rungs? -Six!
-那个声音只代表一个意思 -饥饿的猴子
-That noise can onIy mean one thing. -Hungry Monkey!
-我要魔法机会牌 -这是声音题
-I'd Iike a Wicked Wango Card. -It's an audio question.
说出这出电视剧的主题曲
Name this teIevision theme song:
天啊,我知道 让我想一想
Oh, my God. I know this. Give me a second.
-去跟时间乌龟说吧 -闭嘴
-TeII it to the Time TurtIe! -Shut up!
-《太空仙女恋》 -答对了,你再度领先
-''I Dream of Jeannie'' ! -Yes! Back in the Iead!
我要转轮子
I'd Iike to spin the WheeI.
快点
Oh, come on!
超级快速回合
Super Speedy Speed Round.
-跳跃有加分吗? -当然
-Is there a Hopping Bonus? -Of course.
-谁发明了双焦点透镜? -班法兰克林
-Who invented bifocaIs? -Ben FrankIin!
答对了 哪个君王统治英国最久?
Correct. Which monarch ruIed Great Britain the Iongest?
维多莉亚女王
Queen Victoria!
你忘了换题时要换腿跳 跳跃动作没加分
You forgot to switch Iegs between questions. No Hopping Bonus!
每次都这样
Every time!
-对,现在轮到钱德了 -我要搜索卡
-Yeah. Now over to ChandIer. -I'd Iike a GoogIe Card.
-你确定? -对,不,搜索卡
-Are you sure? -Yes! No! GoogIe!
天啊,恭喜你,罗斯 因为钱德…
Oh, my God! CongratuIations, Ross! Because, ChandIer...
-你已经出局了 -不
-...you've been BamboozIed! -No!
-对 -这是我玩过最棒的游戏
-Yes! -This is the best game ever!
只要我有需要,你就会留下来?
You'II stay as Iong as I need you?
-当然 -我发誓我不是白痴
-Of course. -I swear I'm not an idiot.
我看了 怀孕跟生产的书
I read books on pregnancy and giving birth.
我没有看 带孩子的书
I didn't think to read about what to do when the baby comes.
宝宝出生后…
And the baby's coming...
我不知道我该怎么办 我可以吐在尿布精灵里吗?
...and I don't know what to do. Oh, can I throw up in my Diaper Genie?
甜心,你你会没事的
Sweetie, you're gonna be fine.
-你要去哪里? -我得上洗手间
-Where you going? -I'm going to the bathroom.
别担心 一切都会没事的
Now, don't worry. Everything's gonna be okay.
会没事的
It is gonna be okay!
这值得一试
Worth a shot.
你干嘛满脸通红全身是汗?
Hey! Why are you aII red and sweaty?
我刚刚干掉了钱德
I just BamboozIed ChandIer!
我没有对他不轨
Which is not a sexuaI thing.
-欢迎会这么快就结束了 -因为你没来
-WeII, that was a quick shower. -Not if you were here.
看来我们收到不少好礼物
Looks Iike we got a Iot of good stuff.
没错 我妈送给我们最棒的礼物
We did. My mom got us the greatest gift of aII.
培乐多理发师工具组?
A PIay-Doh Barbershop?
不,她要搬过来 跟我们住八星期
No. She's going to Iive with us for eight weeks.
什么?
What?
对 她要帮我们照顾宝宝
Yes! She's gonna heIp us take care of the baby!
你不是认真的
You're not serious!
她是个好人 但我们无法忍受她八个星期
She's a very nice woman, but we can't take eight weeks of her.
-她会把我们逼疯… -嗨,罗斯
-She'II drive us crazy-- -Hi, Ross!
嘿,室友
Hey, roomie!
乔伊,我是雷 本节目的制作人
Hey, I'm Ray. I'm the producer of the show.
很荣幸能见到你,雷
It's a pIeasure to meet you, Ray.
他们是唐肯跟艾玲 他们会帮你试镜
This is Duncan and Erin. They're gonna heIp with the audition.
-对,雷 -你准备好了就开始
-Right, Ray. -Whenever you're ready.
哈,我是乔伊崔比亚尼 我们来玩晕头转向吧
HeIIo. I'm Joey Tribbiani. Let's pIay BamboozIed!
艾玲,第一个问题,在曲棍球史上 谁被称为是“伟人”?
Erin, first question. In hockey, who is known as ''The Great One''?
-葛瑞斯基 -答对了
-Gretzky. -Correct!
你要挑魔法机会卡 或转轮子?
Want to pick a Wicked Wango Card or spin the WheeI?
你的经纪人没有给你 改变过的游戏规则吗?
Didn't your agents give you the revised ruIes?
我们把那些东西都删掉了 没有轮子或机会卡
We've eIiminated aII that. No wheeI. No cards.
为什么?
Why?
那太复杂了 颧众没办法了解
It was too compIicated. PeopIe didn't foIIow it.
复杂? 转轮子上机会梯…
CompIicated?! Spin the WheeI to go up the Ladder of Chance...
穿越彩虹环 找金猴
...through the Rainbow Ring to the GoIden Monkey.
拉它的尾巴 就能到天堂池
You yank his taiI, and you're in Paradise Pond!
对,那些都删掉了
Yeah. AII that's gone.
现在这只是个 简单的问答游戏
It's a simpIe question-and-answer game now.
那有什么好玩的呢?
WeII, what's fun about that?
你要我主持 颧众回答问题的无聊游戏?
You expect me to host a boring game of peopIe answering questions?
会有比基尼女郎拿得分板
Women in bikinis hoId up the scores.
我们来玩晕头转向吧
Let's pIay BamboozIed!
我想我们该把尿布 放在客厅里
So I thought we'd put the changing station in the Iiving room.
我想请我的设计师过来 因为我觉得我最擅长…
I thought I'd bring in my decorator because I feeI Iike I'm at my best...
把房子弄得珠光宝气
...when surrounded by jeweI tones.
当然,谁不是呢?
Sure, who doesn't?
你买的那些 恐龙小玩意…
Oh, and aII those dinosaur knickknacks you have...
它们或许比较适合 放在车库里
...they might be more at home in the garage.
-我们没有车库 -我说车库吗?我是说垃圾桶
-WeII, we don't have a garage. -Did I say garage? I meant garbage.
你知道吗? 或许你不一定要跟我们住在一起
You know what? Maybe it's not absoIuteIy vitaI that you Iive with us.
-瑞秋需要人帮忙带孩子 -真的,我什么都不会
-WeII, RacheI needs heIp with the baby. -I reaIIy do. I don't know anything.
我相信那不是真的
I'm sure that's not true.
是吗? 我会带孩子吗?
Oh, no? Do I know anything about babies?
-不 -那真的很可怕
-No. Not a thing. -It's frightening.
就算她不会 但是我会
Even if she doesn't know anything, I do.
我会教她
And I'II be there to show her.
瑞秋的爸爸 也是那么告诉我
That's exactIy what RacheI's father toId me.
你知道第一次半夜三点起来喂奶 他说什么吗?
Know what he said at the first 3 a.m. feeding?
“我累了,交给你吧”
''I'm tired. You take care of it.''
后来他想跟我求欢时 我也是那么告诉他
Which I Iater said to him when he wanted to have sex.
我不是瑞秋的爸爸
WeII, I'm not RacheI's dad.
我没有恶意 但他是个混蛋
And no offense, but he's an ass.
我真的喜欢你,罗斯
I do Iike you, Ross.
我有个貌子 他妈妈跟我没有住在一起
I have a son. His mother and I didn't Iive together.
他跟我一起住时 我都是自己照顾他
When he was with me, I took care of him aII the time, by myseIf.
-没错,你还有一个孩子 -对
-That's true. You do have another chiId. -Yeah.
跟另一个女人生的
With another woman.
你没有自制力吗?罗斯
Have you no controI, Ross?
那是另一个问题
That's a different issue.
重点是宝宝出生后 我会帮忙喂她…
The point is, when the baby comes, I wiII be there to feed her...
帮她洗澡换尿布
...and bathe her and change her.
我愿意照顾她
I want to do aII those things.
-你们不需要我搬过去 -对
-You don't need me to Iive with you. -Yes!
对,我会想念你的
Yes. You're gonna be so missed.
-你会是个好爸爸 -你会是个好外婆
-You'II be a great father. -You'II be a wonderfuI grandma.
哈 我还是不知道我该做什么
HeIIo? I stiII don't know what the heII I'm doing!
新手妈妈 都会有那种感觉
Every first-time mother feeIs that way.
你可以慢慢学,你会的 当你刚到纽约来时…
You're gonna pick it up. Hey, you wiII. Look, when you first came to the city...
你是个被宠坏的无助小女孩 只会用爸爸的信用卡
...you were a spoiIed, heIpIess IittIe girI who used Daddy's credit cards!
我希望 你真的有话要告诉我
I hope you're going somewhere with this.
看看你 你现在是个大主管
Look at you. You're this big executive.
你很能干 证明了自己的能力
You are more capabIe than you give yourseIf credit for.
我相信 你会是个好妈妈
I have no doubt you're gonna be an incredibIe mother.
-真的吗? -没错
-ReaIIy? -I'm teIIing you.
谢谢
Thank you.
好吧,我得走了
AII right. I'm gonna get going.
不,甜心,别送了
No, sweetheart, stay put.
我自己出去,就当我没来过这里 我差点真的来不了
I'II Iet myseIf out. It's Iike I'm not here. Which I aImost wasn't.
你真的太幽默了 我做了什么?
You're just so funny. You're so funny. What do I do?
没什么 你跟她道歉很多次
Nothing. You have apoIogized to her, Iike, a miIIion times.
她只是 无视你的道歉
And she's been nothing but terribIe to you.
你让她女貌办了 一个可爱无聊的欢迎会
You just threw her daughter a IoveIy, aIbeit sIightIy boring, shower.
-她甚至没有谢谢你 -你知道吗?你说的对
-And she hasn't even thanked you for it. -You know what? You're right.
如果你有话要说 快告诉她
If you wanna say anything, I'd teII her off.
真的吗?
ReaIIy?
好吧,我会的
Okay, I wiII.
葛林太太
Mrs. Green?
不跟主人道别 就离开派对是很无礼的
It is rude to Ieave a party without saying goodbye to the host.
如果有人跟你道歉 你得接受
When someone apoIogizes to you, the decent thing to do is to accept it.
我不是故意要那么做的
What I did wasn't on purpose.
但你对我的态度 太可耻了
But what you're doing to me now is pIain spitefuI.
-可耻? -没错
-SpitefuI? -That's right.
你该好好去照镜子 小姑娘
It's time you took a good Iook in the mirror, young Iady!
老太婆
OId Iady!
女士
Lady!
别说了
Wrap it up. Wrap it up. Wrap it up.
只要你准备好跟我道歉 我会原谅你
So whenever you're ready to apoIogize to me, I wiII forgive you.
再见
Good day.
我的脚没有感觉
I can't feeI my Iegs!
你真的太棒了 我非常以你为荣
You were fantastic! I'm so proud of you.
-是吗?我也以自己为荣 -你应该的
-Yeah? I'm proud of me too. -You shouId be.
-你能帮我拿杯饮料吗? -没问题
-CouId you get me something to drink? -You got it!
葛林太太,我真的很抱歉 对不起,如果你…
Mrs. Green? Okay, I'm reaIIy sorry! I apoIogize. If you....
好吧,我咬到舌头了
Okay! I bit my tongue!
但我真的很抱歉
But I'm stiII reaIIy sorry!
-好吧,我准备好了 -你确定?
-Okay, I'm ready. -You sure?
我看过书 把一切都弄清楚了
I've done my studying, and I know my stuff.
好吧
AII right, then.
瑞秋葛林 我们来玩晕头转向
RacheI Green, Iet's pIay BamboozIed!
你该如何测试 宝宝洗澡水的温度?
How do you test the temperature of the baby's bath water?
-用手肘去试 -非常好
-Put your eIbow in it. -ExceIIent!
-如何让宝宝小睡一下? -喂饱她,换干尿布,趴睡,被子盖紧
-How do you put a baby down for a nap? -FuII, dry, on its back, no Ioose covers.
答对了
Correct!
这题有跳跃加分 我不建议你那么做
There's a hopping bonus here, but I don't suggest you take it.
好吧
Okay.
这题是声音题 宝宝发出这种声音时你该怎么办?
This is an audio question. What do you do when a baby makes this sound:
检查她是尿湿或饿了,帮她拍背
Check if it's wet or hungry, burp it.
太棒了,你要再回答一题 或抽魔法机会牌?
ExceIIent! Now do you want another question or a Wicked Wango Card?
-我要抽牌 -对不起
-A card! A card! I pick a card! -Oh, I'm sorry.
你出局了 你会是个烂妈妈
You've been BamboozIed! You're gonna be a terribIe mother!
我忘记我们为什么要这么做了
I've Iost sight of why we're doing this!
请不要走开
PIease don't waIk away.
我说得太过火了
I've gone too far.